{
    "id": "57cbcafda47b4999aed9d2e52cd9c9a1",
    "title": "Hear and listen to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "185aac6616814e05bb7e060ca35e7f95",
            "title": "Hear And Listen To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did you …………….. the noise?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I was …………………. the news when they came.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hearing",
                        "listening to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t …………….. you. Can you talk a bit louder?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen",
                        "listen to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ……………… me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen",
                        "listen to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you ………………… about the accident?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t think we can trust him. I have ……………… several strange stories about him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heard",
                        "listened to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You never ………………..  me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "listen",
                        "listen to",
                        "hear"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "No one could …………………. what she said.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hear",
                        "listen",
                        "listen to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ……………….. the dogs barking outside.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "heard",
                        "listened",
                        "listened to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When he speaks, everybody ………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "listens",
                        "listens to",
                        "hears"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}